function 


const question1 = {
    question: "What is the best-selling video game of all time?",
    answer: "Tetris",
}

const question2 = {
    question: 'In what year was the game "Fortnite" first released?',
    answer: "2017",
}

const question3 = {
    question: 'Which company developed the game series "The Legend of Zelda"?',
    answer: "Nintendo",
}

const question4 = {
    question: 'What is the objective of the game "Tetris"?',
    answer: "fitting falling blocks together",
}

const question5 = {
    question: 'Who is the main character in the game "Super Mario Bros."?',
    answer: "Mario",
}

const question6 = {
    question: 'What genre does the game "Counter-Strike" belong to?',
    answer: "FPS",
}

const question7 = {
    question: 'Which popular game features a battle royale mode and is set in the "Call of Duty" universe?',
    answer: "Call of Duty: Warzone",
}

const question8 = {
    question: "What gaming console is produced by Sony Interactive Entertainment?",
    answer: "PlayStation",
}

const question9 = {
    question: 'In the game "Pokémon," what type is effective against water-type Pokémon?',
    answer: "Electric",
}

const question10 = {
    question: "What does RPG stand for in the context of video games?",
    answer: "Role-playing game",
}

var questions = [question1, question2, question3, question4, question5, question6, question7, question8, question9, question10]